North Pacific Program, Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy Records UA189
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject Files, 1981 -- 1996; 1985 -- 1999; UA189.001; 7.2 Linear Feet; 10 Digital Object(s); 280 Kilobytes
  - Mexico-finances, 1995; UA189.001.004.00059 (Box 4)
  - [Newsletter] OB file 92, 1985 -- 1990; UA189.001.004.00060 (Box 4)
  - [Newsletter Attendees], 1989 -- 1990; UA189.001.004.00061 (Box 4)
  - [Newsletter] Post newsletter response, 1992; UA189.001.004.00062 (Box 4)
  - [Newsletter] Fletcher students 1989 - by nation, UA189.001.004.00063 (Box 4)
  - [Newsletter] Yeacher alums-Canada, Japan, ROK, PRC, ROC, CIS, 1990; UA189.001.004.00064 (Box 4)
  - [Newsletter] Alumni publications, 1990; UA189.001.004.00065 (Box 4)
  - [Newsletter '90] Newsletter news 1990 new new new, 1989; UA189.001.004.00066 (Box 4)
  - [Newsletter '90] Bio on speakers, 1989; UA189.001.004.00067 (Box 4)
  - [Newsletter '90] 1991 newsletter news, 1990; UA189.001.004.00068 (Box 4)
  - [Newsletter '90 North Pacific newsletter], 1985; UA189.001.004.00069 (Box 4)
  - [Newsletter '90 North Pacific newsletters 1989], UA189.001.004.00070 (Box 4)
  - [Newsletter '90 North Pacific newsletter 1990], UA189.001.004.00071 (Box 4)
  - [Newsletter '90 North Pacific newsletter 1992], UA189.001.004.00072 (Box 4)
  - [Newsletter '90] Newsletter 1990 1/31/91, 1990 -- 1991; UA189.001.004.00073 (Box 4)
  - [Newsletter '90 North Pacific newsletter 1990 updates], 1990 -- 1991; UA189.001.004.00074 (Box 4)
  - [Newsletter '94] North Pacific Newsletter, 1994; UA189.001.009.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, 6, 9, 84, Folder 3, Box 9)
  - [Newsletter update Newsletter information], 1994; UA189.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - [Newsletter update] Newsletter corrections, 1994 -- 1995; UA189.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - [Newsletter update] Letters/info 11/93-, 1992 -- 1994; UA189.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - [Newspaper articles] Trade, economics APEC, 1994; UA189.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - [Newspaper articles] Articles, 1994; UA189.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - [North Pacific map] Map, 1990; UA189.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - [North Pacific map] Maps, 1990; UA189.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - NPP, 1994; UA189.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - [NPP '93 report Drafts], 1993; UA189.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - [NPP '93 report] Fletcher/Hokkaido report, 1985; UA189.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - [NPP 1994] NPP -, UA189.001.005.00011 (Box 5)
    1 of 14.
  - [NPP 1994] Participant class, UA189.001.005.00012 (Box 5)
    2 of 14.
  - [NPP 1994] NPP '94 correspondence, UA189.001.005.00013 (Box 5)
    3 of 14.
  - [NPP 1994] NPP '94 odds and ends, UA189.001.005.00014 (Box 5)
    4 of 14.
  - [NPP 1994] Visas, UA189.001.005.00015 (Box 5)
    5 of 14.
  - [NPP 1994] Memos to participants, UA189.001.005.00016 (Box 5)
    6 of 14.
  - [NPP 1994] Travel payments, UA189.001.005.00017 (Box 5)
    7 of 14.
  - [NPP 1994] Alumni applicants, UA189.001.005.00018 (Box 5)
    8 of 14.
  - [NPP 1994] Completed visas, UA189.001.005.00019 (Box 5)
    9 of 14.
  - [NPP 1994] 1994 summer seminar applicants, UA189.001.005.00020 (Box 5)
    10 of 14.
  - [NPP 1994] Applications, UA189.001.005.00021 (Box 6)
    11 of 14.
  - [NPP 1994] Flight info Moscow, UA189.001.005.00022 (Box 5)
    12 of 14.
  - [NPP 1994] Travel to Moscow, UA189.001.005.00023 (Box 5)
    13 of 14.
  - [NPP 1994] NPP '94 Moscow waivers, UA189.001.005.00024 (Box 5)
    14 of 14.
  - [NPP '94 (dead)] 1994 Kamchatka, 1993; UA189.001.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - [NPP '94 (dead)] Flight information '94 NPP seminar Kamchatka, 1993; UA189.001.005.00026 (Box 5)
  - [NPP '94 correspondence] 94 NPP Parkansky correspondence, 1994; UA189.001.005.00027 (Box 5)
  - [NPP '94 correspondence] NPP '94 correspondence, 1994; UA189.001.005.00028 (Box 5)
  - NPP '94 report, 1994; UA189.001.005.00029 (Box 5)
  - NPP report, 1991 -- 1992; UA189.001.005.00030 (Box 5)
  - North Pacific Program disk, 1990 -- 1996; UA189.001.005.00031
    - The City in North Pacific History; The Sanwa Lecture Series, 1990; UA189.000622; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Kilobytes
    - Vladivostok: Hopes and Realities, 1990; UA189.000623; 1 Digital Object(s); 23 Kilobytes
    - Russia on the Pacific, circa 1990s; UA189.000624; 1 Digital Object(s); 28 Kilobytes
    - Opening Remarks, Dinner at Ambassador Donald P. Gregg's Residence, 1991; UA189.000625; 1 Digital Object(s); 29 Kilobytes
    - 1992 Summer Seminar: What is a Leader?, UA189.000626; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Kilobytes
    - The North Pacific Program: A Pedagogical Pattern, A Specific Theme: Leadership, 1993; UA189.000627; 1 Digital Object(s); 42 Kilobytes
    - Tow Leaders of Modern Asia: Li Hung-Chang and Hara Kei, 1993; UA189.000628; 1 Digital Object(s); 19 Kilobytes
    - The Fletcher Summer Seminar Moscow, 1994-July; UA189.000629; 1 Digital Object(s); 41 Kilobytes
    - Introduction, 1994; UA189.000630; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Kilobytes
    - EIB B230: International Business Strategy & Operations, Spring 1996; UA189.000631; 1 Digital Object(s); 48 Kilobytes
  - Odds and ends, 1994; UA189.001.005.00032 (Box 5)
  - Qmodem, 1993; UA189.001.005.00033 (Box 5)
    Contained in folder is a floppy disk with the software program 'Qmodem'.
  - [Romanov research] Romanovs, 1995; UA189.001.005.00034 (Box 5)
    [1 of 2]
  - [Romanov research] Romanovs, 1995; UA189.001.005.00035 (Box 5)
  - Sanwa, 1990 -- 1992; UA189.001.005.00036 (Box 5)
  - [Sanwa], 1992 -- 1993; UA189.001.005.00037 (Box 5)
  - [Sanwa] Speakers, 1992 -- 1993; UA189.001.005.00038 (Box 5)
  - [Sanwa] Rhoads Murphey Sanwa, 1990; UA189.001.005.00039 (Box 5)
  - [Sanwa] Kevin Starr, 1990; UA189.001.005.00040 (Box 5)
  - [Sanwa] Fliers, 1990; UA189.001.005.00041 (Box 5)
  - [Sanwa '90] Sanwa Lecture Series, "The City in North Pacific History" program, 1990; UA189.001.009.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, 6, 9, 84, Folder 1, Box 9)
  - [Sanwa '92] Sanwa 1991 Nakahara, 1990 -- 1992; UA189.001.005.00042 (Box 5)
  - [Sanwa '92] Sanwa Lecture Series, "Japan in Southeast Asia" program, 1992; UA189.001.009.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, 6, 9, 84, Folder 2, Box 9)
  - [Sanwa 1993 publications] Constantine V. Pleshakov, UA189.001.005.00043 (Box 5)
  - [Sanwa 1993 publications] Constantine V. Pleshakov-articles, 1992; UA189.001.005.00044 (Box 5)
  - [Sanwa '94 Synopsis], 1994; UA189.001.005.00045 (Box 5)
  - [Sanwa '94 Bureau of Intelligence and Research], 1995; UA189.001.005.00046 (Box 5)
  - [Sanwa '94] Sanwa '94 speakers, 1994 -- 1995; UA189.001.005.00047 (Box 5)
  - [Sanwa '94] ]94 Sanwa lectures originals, 1994; UA189.001.005.00048 (Box 5)
  - [Sanwa mailing] Sanwa lecture series info, 1987 -- 1988; UA189.001.005.00049 (Box 5)
  - [Sanwa mailing] Information, 1989; UA189.001.005.00050 (Box 5)
  - Sanwa photos-Stephan, 1990; UA189.001.005.00051 (Box 5)
    This folder contain negatives.
  - Sanwa Research Institute, 1992; UA189.001.005.00052 (Box 5)
  - [Sapporo brochures], 1989; UA189.001.005.00053 (Box 5)
  - [Sasakawa Peace Foundation], 1990; UA189.001.005.00054 (Box 5)
  - [Seoul] Seoul itineraries, 1991; UA189.001.005.00055 (Box 5)
  - [Seoul] Korean language, 1991; UA189.001.005.00056 (Box 5)
  - [Seoul 1991] Incoming Korea, 1990 -- 1991; UA189.001.005.00057 (Box 5)
  - [Seoul 1991] Schedules, announcements Korea, UA189.001.005.00058 (Box 5)
  - [Seoul 1991] Japanese/Seoul, UA189.001.005.00059 (Box 5)
  - [Seoul 1991] Institute handouts, UA189.001.005.00060 (Box 5)
  - [Seoul 1991] Post seoul correspondence, UA189.001.005.00061 (Box 5)
  - [Seoul 1991] JCP corresp Korea, UA189.001.005.00062 (Box 5)
  - [Seoul 1991] Travel-Korea, UA189.001.005.00063 (Box 5)
  - [Seoul 1991] Intersect, UA189.001.005.00064 (Box 5)
  - [Seoul 1991] Part. addresses, UA189.001.005.00065 (Box 5)
  - [Seoul conf 9/94] Korea articles, 1994; UA189.001.005.00066 (Box 5)
  - [Seoul conf. 9/94] Schedule, 1994; UA189.001.005.00067 (Box 5)
  - [Seoul conf. 9/94] APEC-Cheju, 1994; UA189.001.005.00068 (Box 5)
  - [Seoul conf. 9/94] Seoul conference 9/94, 1994; UA189.001.005.00069 (Box 5)
  - [Seoul correspondence] KCR corresp. Korea, 1991; UA189.001.005.00070 (Box 5)
  - [Seoul correspondence] Han Sung Soo, 1990 -- 1992; UA189.001.005.00071 (Box 5)
  - [Seoul NPP] sEOUL/prc, 1991; UA189.001.005.00072 (Box 5)
  - [Seoul NPP] List-participants, 1991; UA189.001.005.00073 (Box 5)
  - [Seoul NPP] Impressiones, 1991; UA189.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - [Seoul NPP] Information, 1991; UA189.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
    4 of 4. Note on folder says 'contemp Korean and study of wider descriptions of the city'.
  - Spare infor, 1995; UA189.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Speakers, 1993 -- 1994; UA189.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Soviety info, 1986; UA189.001.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Tax statement, 1990 -- 1991; UA189.001.006.00006 (Box 5)
  - [Toho Life Insurance Correspondence], 1989 -- 1994; UA189.001.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - [Toho Life Insurance] Budget, 1988 -- 1989; UA189.001.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - [Toho Life Insurance Correspondence], 1990 -- 1991; UA189.001.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - [Toho Life Insurance Correspondence], 1989; UA189.001.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - [USA] Alaska, 1990 -- 1991; UA189.001.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - [USA] Hawaii, 1989; UA189.001.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - [USA] Abroad and beyond, 1990; UA189.001.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - [USSR] Efanov-occasional paper Cowper-fed, 1991; UA189.001.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - [USSR] SFE Boris Alexander, 1990 -- 1992; UA189.001.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock] Vladivostock outlines student, 1990; UA189.001.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock] Itineraries/emerg #'s Vlad, 1992; UA189.001.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock] Visa info, 1992; UA189.001.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock] Papers, 1992; UA189.001.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock] CV's Vlad list, 1992; UA189.001.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock] Vlad-Japan, 1992; UA189.001.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock II] Vlad II report and Sanwa responses, 1993; UA189.001.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock II] Applications Vladivostock, 1992; UA189.001.006.00023 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock 1990] Final advice and misc. infor-Vladivostock, UA189.001.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock 1990 Topics], UA189.001.006.00025 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock 1990] Karin, UA189.001.006.00026 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock 1990] Vladivostock vital stats, 1989; UA189.001.006.00027 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock 1990] Vladivostock list, UA189.001.006.00028 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock 1990 Notes], UA189.001.006.00029 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock 1990] Vladivostock needs assessment, UA189.001.006.00030 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock 1990] Vladivostock - Boston sister city, UA189.001.006.00031 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock 1990 Cooperative Russian language program], 1989 -- 1991; UA189.001.006.00032 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock 1990] Vladivostock - Hokkaido application descriptions, UA189.001.006.00033 (Box 6)
    5 of 5. Note on folders says ' take data sheet and application form'.
  - [Vlad 1990] Press-Vladivostock, UA189.001.006.00034 (Box 6)
  - [Vlad 1990] Post Vlad correspondence, UA189.001.006.00035 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock 1992] Rus. newspaper articles, UA189.001.006.00036 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock 1992] Misc. Vladivostock seminar, UA189.001.006.00037 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock 1992] Letters from Russians, 1991 -- 1992; UA189.001.006.00038 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock 1992] Pictures and press - from library display Vlad, UA189.001.006.00039 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock 1992] Russian language, UA189.001.006.00040 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock 1992] Soviet visa forms, UA189.001.006.00041 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock correspondence 1991-1992] JCP out corresp via KCR computer Spring, UA189.001.006.00042 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock correspondence 1991-1992] Post Vlad '92 corres, UA189.001.006.00043 (Box 6)
  - [Vladivostock correspondence 1991-1992] Japanese film info (return to KCR), UA189.001.006.00044 (Box 6)
  - [Vlad report drafts] Responses to retro cities etc, 1991; UA189.001.006.00045 (Box 6)
  - [Vlad report drafts] Drafts, 1990; UA189.001.006.00046 (Box 6)
  - [Vlad report drafts] Vlad report, 1990; UA189.001.006.00047 (Box 6)
  - [Vlad seminar 1992] Protocol, UA189.001.006.00048 (Box 6)
    1 of 10. Note on front of folder says 'cost proposal'.
  - [Vlad seminar 1992] Vlad - Korea, UA189.001.006.00049 (Box 6)
  - [Vlad seminar 1992] China - Vlad, UA189.001.006.00050 (Box 6)
  - [Vlad seminar 1992] Descr. Vlad, UA189.001.006.00051 (Box 6)
  - [Vlad seminar 1992] Seminar 1992 corresp, UA189.001.006.00052 (Box 6)
  - [Vlad seminar 1992] Memo, UA189.001.006.00053 (Box 6)
    6 of 10.
  - [Vlad seminar 1992] Meetings itin., UA189.001.006.00054 (Box 6)
  - [Vlad seminar 1992] Vlad meeting 3/26/92, UA189.001.006.00055 (Box 6)
  - [Vlad seminar 1992 Far east branch of the Academy of Sciences in the USSR], UA189.001.006.00056 (Box 6)
  - [Vlas seminar 1992] Vlad accecptance, UA189.001.006.00057 (Box 6)
  - [Vlad.-seminar 1992] Soviet correspondence, UA189.001.006.00058 (Box 6)
  - [Vlad.-seminar 1992] Russian Far East news, UA189.001.006.00059 (Box 6)
  - [Vlad.-seminar 1992] Info-Vlad-maps, UA189.001.006.00060 (Box 6)
  - [Vlad.-seminar 1992] Vlad. city report, UA189.001.006.00061 (Box 6)
  - [Vlad.-seminar 1992] Business selections, UA189.001.006.00062 (Box 6)
  - [Vlad.-seminar 1992] USSR-Vlad, UA189.001.006.00063 (Box 6)
  - [Vlad.-seminar 1992 Jan M. Presser paper], UA189.001.006.00064 (Box 6)
- Audiovisual materials, 1985 -- 1994; 1985 -- 1999; UA189.002; 2.4 Linear Feet
  This series includes photographs and videocassettes documenting the North Pacific Program from 1985 to 1995. The bulk of the photographs are from the annual field seminar and the videocassettes also feature lectures from the seminar. The majority of the photographs are labeled as to which year they were taken but few have any people identified.
  This series is arranged loosely chronologically.
  - Hokkaido 1985 pictures [1 of 3], UA189.002.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Hokkaido 1985 pictures [2 of 5], UA189.002.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Hokkaido 1985 pictures [3 of 5], UA189.002.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - Hokkaido 1988 pictures [1 of 2], UA189.002.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Hokkaido 1988 pictures [2 of 2], UA189.002.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Ah So! journ through Japanese hand gestures '89 Fletcher Hokkaido Program, 1989; UA189.002.007.00006 (Box 7)
    The brand name for this VHS cassette is TDK super avilyn high quality standard HS.
    videocassette
  - Fletcher Hokkaido Program '89 North Pacific International Forum [1 of 3], 1989; UA189.002.007.00007 (Box 7)
    The brand name of this VHS cassette is Sony.
  - Fletcher Hokkaido Program '89 North Pacific International Program [2 of 3], 1989; UA189.002.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - Fletcher Hokkaido Program '89 North Pacific International Program [3 of 3], 1989; UA189.002.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - [1989] Kate misc photos [1 of 8], UA189.002.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - [1989] [2 of 8], UA189.002.007.00011 (Box 7)
  - [1989] Hokkaido '89 [3 of 8], UA189.002.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - [1989] [4 of 8], UA189.002.007.00013 (Box 7)
  - [1989] [5 of 8], UA189.002.007.00014 (Box 7)
  - [1989] [6 of 8], UA189.002.007.00015 (Box 7)
  - [1989] [7 of 8], UA189.002.007.00016 (Box 7)
  - [1989] Theresa [8 of 8], UA189.002.007.00017 (Box 7)
  - [1990-1994] [1 of 5], UA189.002.007.00018 (Box 7)
  - [1990-1994] [2 of 5], UA189.002.007.00019 (Box 7)
  - [1990-1994] [3 of 5], UA189.002.007.00020 (Box 7)
    There is also a brochure from the 1994 APEC seminar in this folder.
  - [1990-1994] [4 of 5], UA189.002.007.00021 (Box 7)
  - [1990-1994] [5 of 5], UA189.002.007.00022 (Box 7)
  - [1990] June [1 of 7], UA189.002.007.00023 (Box 7)
  - [1990] June [2 of 7], UA189.002.007.00024 (Box 7)
  - [1990] July [3 of 7], UA189.002.007.00025 (Box 7)
  - [1990] July [4 of 7], UA189.002.007.00026 (Box 7)
  - [1990] July [5 of 7], UA189.002.007.00027 (Box 7)
  - [1990] July [6 of 7], UA189.002.007.00028 (Box 7)
  - [1990] August [7 of 7], UA189.002.007.00029 (Box 7)
  - Pictures for report Vlad, 1990; UA189.002.007.00030 (Box 7)
  - Photos 1990 - Five yr. retrospective, UA189.002.007.00031 (Box 7)
  - Vladivostock 1990 pictures [1 of 4], UA189.002.007.00032 (Box 7)
  - Vladivostock 1990 pictures [2 of 4], UA189.002.007.00033 (Box 7)
  - Vladivostock 1990 pictures [3 of 4], UA189.002.007.00034 (Box 7)
  - Vladivostock 1990 pictures [4 of 4], UA189.002.007.00035 (Box 7)
  - Seoul pics 1991 [1 of 16], UA189.002.007.00036 (Box 7)
  - Seoul pics 1991 [2 of 16], UA189.002.007.00037 (Box 7)
  - Seoul pics 1991 [3 of 16], UA189.002.007.00038 (Box 7)
  - Seoul pics 1991 [4 of 16], UA189.002.007.00039 (Box 7)
  - Seoul pics 1991 [5 of 16], UA189.002.007.00040 (Box 7)
  - Seoul pics 1991 [6 of 16], UA189.002.007.00041 (Box 7)
  - Seoul pics 1991 [7 of 16], UA189.002.007.00042 (Box 7)
  - Seoul pics 1991 [8 of 16], UA189.002.007.00043 (Box 7)
  - Seoul pics 1991 [9 of 16], UA189.002.007.00044 (Box 7)
  - Seoul pics 1991 [10 of 16], UA189.002.007.00045 (Box 7)
  - Seoul pics 1991 [11 of 16], UA189.002.007.00046 (Box 7)
  - Seoul pics 1991 [12 of 16], UA189.002.007.00047 (Box 7)
  - Seoul pics 1991 [13 of 16], UA189.002.007.00048 (Box 7)
  - Seoul pics 1991 [14 of 16], UA189.002.007.00049 (Box 7)
  - Seoul pics 1991 [15 of 16], UA189.002.007.00050 (Box 7)
  - Seoul pics 1991 [16 of 16], UA189.002.007.00051 (Box 7)
  - 1992 July JCP - Bigelow + HI, 1, UA189.002.008.00001 (Box 8)
  - 1992 July SHP Korea train to VLAD., Lawrence of Khab, 2, UA189.002.008.00002 (Box 8)
  - 1992 July Libiamo July 18th, 3, UA189.002.008.00003 (Box 8)
  - 1992 July JCP birthday, VLAD 1992, picnic, 4, UA189.002.008.00004 (Box 8)
  - 1992 July Expedition 1. Yuki, picnic, church, 5, UA189.002.008.00005 (Box 8)
  - 1992 July Talent night, 6, UA189.002.008.00006 (Box 8)
  - 1992 July Peace cttee, country restaurant, 7, UA189.002.008.00007 (Box 8)
  - July 1992 Leaving Vladivostock, Khabarovsk navy day, 8, 1993; UA189.002.008.00008 (Box 8)
  - 1993 [1 of 6], UA189.002.008.00009 (Box 8)
  - 1993 [2 of 6], UA189.002.008.00010 (Box 8)
  - 1993 [3 of 6], UA189.002.008.00011 (Box 8)
  - 1993 [4 of 6], UA189.002.008.00012 (Box 8)
  - 1993 [5 of 6], UA189.002.008.00013 (Box 8)
  - 1993 [6 of 6], UA189.002.008.00014 (Box 8)
  - Moscow '94, 1994; UA189.002.008.00015 (Box 8)
  - Dean Galvinetal, Stephan, 1990; UA189.002.008.00016 (Box 8)
    The brand name of this VHS cassette is TDK Memorex HS.
  - Fletcher/ N. Pacific photos, 1991; UA189.002.008.00017 (Box 8)
    Also included in this folder is a brochure from the Daewoo Corporation.
  - Leaving Russia last pictures, 1992; UA189.002.008.00018 (Box 8)
  - NPP, 1990; UA189.002.008.00019 (Box 8)
  - NPP, 1990; UA189.002.008.00020 (Box 8)
  - NPP, 1990; UA189.002.008.00021 (Box 8)
  - NPP, 1990; UA189.002.008.00022 (Box 8)
  - NPP, 1990; UA189.002.008.00023 (Box 8)
  - NPP, 1990; UA189.002.008.00024 (Box 8)
  - Photos for Halftones, 1990; UA189.002.008.00025 (Box 8)
  - [R.M. Vitonye], 1990; UA189.002.008.00026 (Box 8)
  - [Untitled], 1990; UA189.002.008.00027 (Box 8)
  - [Untitled], 1990; UA189.002.008.00028 (Box 8)
  - [Untitled], 1990; UA189.002.008.00029 (Box 8)
  - [Untitled], 1990; UA189.002.008.00030 (Box 8)
  - [Untitled], 1990; UA189.002.008.00031 (Box 8)
  - [Untitled], 1990; UA189.002.008.00032 (Box 8)
  - [Untitled], 1990; UA189.002.008.00033 (Box 8)
  - [Untitled], 1990; UA189.002.008.00034 (Box 8)
  - [Untitled], 1990; UA189.002.008.00035 (Box 8)
  - [Untitled], 1990; UA189.002.008.00036 (Box 8)
  - [Untitled], 1990; UA189.002.008.00037 (Box 8)
  - [Untitled], 1990; UA189.002.008.00038 (Box 8)
- John Perry records, 1980 -- 2018; UA189.003; 3.1 Linear Feet
  This series contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
  This series contains original correspondence, seminar schedules and trip itineraries, reports, budgets, and audiocassette tapes of lectures at the Fletcher School's North Pacific Program (NPP). These materials were created or collected by John C. Perry, who founded the NPP and taught East Asian and Maritime Studies at the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy from 1980 - 2015. The majority of the materials consist of correspondence between Perry and his international colleagues and students. The series also contains information about guest lecturers from the Sanwa Lecture Series, which was run by the NPP. The bulk of this series was created from 1980 - 2018.
  This series is arranged in received order.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Gift of John C. Perry, 2018, accession MS-2019-042.
  - Mexico Summer Seminar, 1995; UA189.003.010.00001; 2 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
  - NPP Seminar Seoul, 1991; UA189.003.010.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Dr. Constantine Pleshakov Sanwa, 1989 -- 1992; UA189.003.010.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Trip round the world, 1988-04; UA189.003.010.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Hokkaido/Sapporo, 1984 -- 1985; UA189.003.010.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Alaska, 1985-07; UA189.003.010.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - TYO/Moscow, 1987-04; UA189.003.010.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Summer interests internships, 1990; UA189.003.010.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Hakodate, 1995 -- 1996; UA189.003.010.00009; 3 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 10-12)
  - Soviet Peace Committee, 1991; UA189.003.010.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Fletcher-Hokkaido brief history, 1984 -- 1991; UA189.003.010.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - NPP Seminar unedited draft report, 1997; UA189.003.010.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - NPP annual report to the Dean, 1982 -- 1994; UA189.003.010.00013; 2 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 16-17)
  - Correspondence, 1985 -- 1986; UA189.003.010.00014; 3 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 18-20)
  - Prospective summer seminar in Rok, circa 1990s -- 2000s; UA189.003.010.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Korea, 1982-10; UA189.003.010.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Budget Hokkaido, 1989 -- 1990; UA189.003.010.00017; 2 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 23-24)
  - Fletcher-Hokkaido application, 1987 -- 1988; UA189.003.010.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - NPP database, 1997; UA189.003.010.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Kate Ryan Hokkaido budget, 1990 -- 1991; UA189.003.010.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence KCR F-H, 1987 -- 1988; UA189.003.010.00021; 2 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 28-29)
  - Workshop topics Hokkaido, 1990; UA189.003.010.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Sapporo cost of living differential, 1990; UA189.003.010.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - NPP seminar working papers, 1997; UA189.003.010.00024; 2 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - NPP, 1993; UA189.003.010.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Hokkaido-NPI Notes, 1990 -- 1991; UA189.003.010.00026; 2 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 34-35)
  - Occasional Papers on Philanthropy, circa 1990s -- 2000s; UA189.003.010.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Vladivostok Seminar, 1990; UA189.003.010.00028; 2 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 37-38)
  - Future summer seminars, 1990; UA189.003.010.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Hokkaido forum corresp., 1990; UA189.003.010.00030; 2 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 40-41)
  - North Pacific Program, 1996; UA189.003.010.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - YPO Young President's Organization, 1982 -- 1983; UA189.003.010.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Sakuma Seminar, 1982 -- 1985; UA189.003.010.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Maui Conference, 1981 -- 1984; UA189.003.010.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Soros Foundation Alla, 1990; UA189.003.010.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Nippon Foundation, 1997 -- 2001; UA189.003.010.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 47-48)
  - NPP summer workshop in Hakodate, 1997; UA189.003.010.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Fletcher-Hokkaido booklets, 1985 -- 1989; UA189.003.010.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 50)